[
    {
    "option1": "We going.",
    "option2": "We are going.",
    "option3": "We go.",
    "option4": "We are go.",
    "question": "আমরা যাই",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We are going.",
    "option2": "We going.",
    "option3": "We are gone.",
    "option4": "We shall go.",
    "question": "আমরা যাচ্ছি",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We go.",
    "option2": "We shall going.",
    "option3": "We have gone.",
    "option4": "We shall go.",
    "question": "আমরা যাবো",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We gone.",
    "option2": "We are gone.",
    "option3": "We have gone.",
    "option4": "We are going.",
    "question": "আমরা গিয়েছি",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We are not go.",
    "option2": "We do not go.",
    "option3": "We have not go.",
    "option4": "We have no go.",
    "question": "আমরা যাই না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We do not going.",
    "option2": "We have not gone.",
    "option3": "We are not gone.",
    "option4": "We are not going.",
    "question": "আমরা যাচ্ছি না",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We shall not go.",
    "option2": "We are not going.",
    "option3": "We have not gone.",
    "option4": "We do not go.",
    "question": "আমরা যাবো না",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We are gone.",
    "option2": "We went.",
    "option3": "We did go.",
    "option4": "We had gone.",
    "question": "আমরা গিয়েছিলাম",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We were going.",
    "option2": "We have going.",
    "option3": "We are gone.",
    "option4": "We had going.",
    "question": "আমরা যাচ্ছিলাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We not go.",
    "option2": "We did not went.",
    "option3": "We did not go.",
    "option4": "We have not went.",
    "question": "আমরা যাই নি",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We may gone.",
    "option2": "We should go.",
    "option3": "We have gone.",
    "option4": "We can go.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারি",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We had not go.",
    "option2": "We shall not go.",
    "option3": "We can not go.",
    "option4": "We do not go.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারি না",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Do we go ?",
    "option2": "Do we are going ?",
    "option3": "Do we going ?",
    "option4": "Do we are go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যাই ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Do we not go ?",
    "option2": "Do we are not going ?",
    "option3": "Do we have not go ?",
    "option4": "Do we have not going ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যাই না ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Have we going ?",
    "option2": "Have we are gone ?",
    "option3": "Have we are going ?",
    "option4": "Have we gone ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি গিয়েছি ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Have we not gone ?",
    "option2": "Have we are not gone ?",
    "option3": "Have we are not went ?",
    "option4": "Have we not went ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি গেছি না/ গিয়েছি না ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Did we went ?",
    "option2": "Did we go ?",
    "option3": "Had we gone ?",
    "option4": "Had we went ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি গিয়েছিলাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Did we not went ?",
    "option2": "Did we have not gone ?",
    "option3": "Did we not go ?",
    "option4": "Did we have not went ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যাই নি ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can we gone ?",
    "option2": "May we go ?",
    "option3": "Shall we go ?",
    "option4": "Do we go ?",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারি কি ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We can go.",
    "option2": "We shall go.",
    "option3": "We will go.",
    "option4": "We should go.",
    "question": "আমাদের যাওয়া উচিত",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can we go ?",
    "option2": "Shall we go ?",
    "option3": "May we go ?",
    "option4": "Did we go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যাবো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We can go.",
    "option2": "We only shall go.",
    "option3": "We shall go.",
    "option4": "We have gone.",
    "question": "আমরাই যাবো",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We must go.",
    "option2": "We may go.",
    "option3": "We shall go.",
    "option4": "We did go.",
    "question": "আমাদের যেতেই হবে",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can not we go ?",
    "option2": "Did not we go ?",
    "option3": "Will we go ?",
    "option4": "Shall we not go ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যাবো না ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]